What's the problem?
何が困るの?
No, that
いや、その
...
Isn't that what happens when you make friends?
友 達とかに 生まれるじゃないですか
That's a good thing.
いいことじゃん
I'm not happy.
嬉しくないです
Nice to meet you like that.
あんなに会えたろ
If we had feelings, wouldn't we have met?
気持ちがあったら会えたんじゃねえの?
It's a little bit out there.
出回るのはちょっと
That's why I came here today to check out the video.
だから今日、動画検証しててこっち来たんだな
Do you want me to verify the video?
動画検証してほしいの?
I want it to disappear.
消してほしいです
So don't ask me anything nice.
じゃあ何でもいいこと聞くな
It's okay.
いいんだろ
It's okay!
いいんだろ!
yes.
はい
Once again, you can do whatever you want.
もう一回、好き勝手していいって
You can do whatever you want.
好き勝手していいです
You have a nice body, don't you?
いい体してんじゃねえかよ
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいか?
Don't you feel uncomfortable?
気持ちくねえのか?
Which one feels better?
どっちが気持ちいいか?
ど っち が 気持ちいいか?
Which one feels better?
どっちが気持ちいいか?
You're riding a little loosely.
ちょっとゆるく乗ってるじゃん
It's great.
えらいよ
Say that from the beginning.
最初からそう言えよ
Why can't I say it?
なんで言えないんだよ
Then say it.
それから言えよ
Do you know what will happen if you can't say it?
言えないとどうなるか分かってる?
yes.
はい
Isn't it facing down?
下にしてんじゃねえか?
Show me from there.
そこから見せてよ
Try posing.
ポーズしてみろよ
Try a good pose.
いいポーズしてみる
I asked her to take off a lot of clothes for me.
私でたくさん脱いでくださいって
hear?
聞こえる?
Please take off a lot of clothes for me.
私でたくさん脱いでください
Isn't your face stinging?
顔にチクリしてんじゃねえか
Because I like chikuri.
チクリ好きなんだから
Hey!
おい!
Reply next time!
次返事しろよ!
Why didn't you reply?
なんで返事しなかったんだ?
You like chikuri, right?
チクリ好きなんだろ?
I like it.
好きです
I did it because I liked it.
好 きかってやってんだよな
Don't tell me what's bothering you.
悩むこと言わせんなよ
Handmade.
手つけ
Isn't that a nice thing to do?
いいけつしてんじゃねえか
Do you like it?
好きなのか?
Head this way.
こっち向けよ
Why aren't you heading this way?
なんでこっち向かねえんだよ
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいの?
Don't lie!
嘘つくんじゃねえよ!
It hurts!
痛いだろ!
It doesn't feel good!
気持ちよくねえだろ!
I screamed.
叫んだよ
Why did you lie?
なんで嘘ついたんだよ
it hurts!
痛い!
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいんだろ?
気 持ちいいんだろ?
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいんだろ?
Why are you lying again?
なんで嘘ついてんだよまた
Don't lie.
嘘つくなよ
Why did you lie?
なん で嘘ついたんだ?
sorry.
すみません
ごめんなさい
That's right, my waist is fine.
腰ちゃんとそれよ
You can't look cute unless you expose your ass.
けつ出さないと可愛く見えねえんだよ
Show me your collar.
首輪を見せろよ
首輪を見せるんだよ
Oh, it's easy to kick ass.
おっと、けつ叩きやすいよね
Take off your pants.
パンツ脱げ
By yourself.
自分で
For this one.
こっち向け
Take off your clothes.
えろく脱ぐんだよ
It's dirty, isn't it?
汚れてんじゃねえか
Clean it up.
きれいにしろよ
Clean it yourself.
自分できれいにしろよ
Isn't it dirty?
汚ねえか
What are you licking?
何舐めてんの?
Eat it.
食わろ
What does it taste like?
何味なんだ?
It's salty.
しょっぱいです
Is it salad flavor?
サラダ味か?
salad?
サラダ?
good.
うまい
It must be good.
うまいんだろ
I'll have you look at it a lot.
いっぱい見てもらう
Pathetic appearance.
情けない姿
Look ahead.
前 見ろ
Lower your back more.
もっと腰を落とせ
Keep it there.
そこでキープだ
Forward.
前向け
You lower your back.
お前腰を落とせ
What is it?
なんすんだねえよ
You're deeper than that.
お前、ちゃんともっと深くだよ
Keep it there.
そこでキープすんだよ
It's just like that.
そのままだぞ
Wow, I'm a pussy.
すげえ、マンコしてんだ
Why did you just say that?
何勝手に言ってんだよ
Drop your hips deeper.
もっと腰を深く落とせよ
Lactic acid has accumulated.
乳酸溜まってきたろ
I was hit hard.
上く刺されたよ
I won't stop.
やめないぞ
Head this way.
こっち向けよ
I thought I'd go once and be done with it.
一回行ったら終わりだと思ってたろ
Let's talk.
喋れよ
That's you.
そんなお前
It's a normal blow job.
普通のフェラだ
Eat more bears.
もっとクマで食わろよ
Eat it, you.
食わろよ、お前
I threw it away for nothing.
何にも捨ててんだよ
More are coming.
もっと来たぞ
Food.
食 わろ
It's not enough, you.
足んねえだろ、お前
Tell me.
口出せ
Please help me.
お手伝ってよ
Don't shut up.
手黙らないで
Open your mouth.
口開けろよ
Put your hands down.
手下ろせ
Open your mouth.
口開けろ
Why is that dirty?
なんでそれ汚いの?
Is it not possible?
出来ないのか?
I can't.
出来ない
You'll be eaten even more.
も っと 食われるんだ
I'm starting to be able to eat properly.
ちゃんと食われるようになってきたね
It feels good, right?
気持ちいいだろ?
Are you happy?
嬉しいか?
You're cutting corners.
手抜いてんだよ
Don't cut corners.
手抜くんじゃねえよ
you.
お前
That's right.
当たってんのだ
Your face is starting to look nice.
いい顔になってきたね
It's dirty.
汚いな
Your face is starting to look nice.
いい顔になってきたね
It's not over yet.
まだ終わんねえぞ
Lick it.
舐めておれ
It's my sister's tour.
お姉のツアーだろ
I'm starting to be able to eat properly.
ちゃんと食われるようになってきたね
you.
お前
Don't rest.
休むなよ
Your face is starting to look nice.
いい顔になってきたね
You look nice.
いい顔だぞ
You can do it if you try.
やれば出来る
Lick it properly.
ちゃんと舐めておれ
You're going to lick it.
ペロペロするんだね
Let's lick it together.
一緒に舐めておれ
Which one did you lick?
どっちから舐めた?
decide?
決める?
Both.
どっちも
You can't come in.
入んねえだろ
I want to lick them both.
どっちも舐めたいんだよ
It's because of negligence.
手抜けからだな
enter.
入ります
you!
お前!
Your face is starting to look nice.
いい 顔になってきたね
good.
いいぞ
It's beautiful.
美しいよ
Look, this is your reward.
ほら、これ報酬だよ
Pick it up.
拾え
Pick it up properly.
ちゃんと拾えよ
You want me to delete the video, right?
動画消して欲しいんだろ?
Don't just proceed on your own.
勝 手に進むんじゃねえよ
Go back.
戻れ
Why is it so dirty?
なんでこんなに汚いんだ?
You want me to delete the video, right?
動画消して欲しいんだろ?
Apologize properly.
ちゃんと謝れよ
Do you know how to apologize?
謝 り方わかんのか?
Please delete the video.
動画消してください
please.
お願いします
Hey.
ねえ
Get your head on.
頭つけろ
Isn't that good?
いいじゃねえかよ
Then look up.
じゃあ顔上げろ
That's it.
あれだね
movie.
動画
I want it to disappear.
消して欲しいんだよ
yes.
はい
I made more noise.
もっと騒しました
I'll erase it.
消してやるよ
yes.
はい
Well then, let's move a little.
じゃあちょっと場所移動しようか
That's exactly four years ago.
ちゃんと4つ前だろ
I crawled.
ハイハイしたよ
It's high.
ハイハイだよ
Walk with a crawl, properly.
ハイハイで歩くんだよ、ちゃんと
Don't stand, don't stand.
立つな、立つな
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
ほい、ほい、ほい、ほい
I'm lost.
迷子なんだよ
It's this way.
こっちだぞ
I'm a little tired.
ちょっと、疲れてるな
I'm tired.
疲れてる
Let's get some hydration together, shall we?
ちょっと水分補給、一緒にするか
You like this, right?
これ好きだろ?
Is it alcohol?
お酒ですか?
You like this, right?
これ好きなんだろ?
Yes, I like it.
はい、好きです
Then let's drink.
じゃあ飲めよ
Oh, were you thirsty?
おー、喉が空いてたのか
But if it's a dog, it's something they usually drink as a snack.
でも 犬だったら、 普通におつまみの場合で飲むんだよな
I'll just lick it downstairs and drink it.
下でペロペロして飲むんだよな
Aren't you going to lick it downstairs and drink it?
下でペロペロして飲むんじゃねえの?
Dogs don't chew and drink, right?
犬は噛んで飲まないだろ?
That's right.
そう ですよ
Make more noise.
もっとピチャピチャ音を立てろよ
Drink deliciously.
おい しそうに飲め
Do you need a reward?
ご褒美いるか?
Reward.
ご褒美
I want a reward.
ご 褒美欲しいよな
This is my favorite jerky.
これ好きなジャーキーだぞ
It's bait.
餌だぞ
It tastes like rice.
ご飯味なんだよ
I've been fed, so please tell me what you think.
餌もらってんだから、ちゃんと感想を言えよ
It should be more delicious.
もっとおいしくなよ
Hey, don't run away.
おい、逃げんな
Don't run away.
逃げてんじゃねえよ
Which jerky was delicious?
どっちのジャーキーが美味しかったんだ?
Both were delicious.
どっちも美味しかった
Which jerky game do you want?
どっちがお前が欲しいジャーキーゲームやるか?
Which one should I choose?
どれにしちゃうかな?
Choose.
選べよ
Is that the jerky on the right?
右のジャーキーか?
Which jerky do you want?
どっちのジャーキーがお前が欲しいジャーキー?
Choose quickly!
早く選べよ!
I can't choose.
選べないです
Well then, both.
じゃあ、どっちも
Go first, go.
先攻、行きます
I'll have it.
いただきますわ
I'll enjoy having this.
いただきます
Hey, does it feel good?
おい、気持ちいい?
Does your mouth feel good?
口まんこ気持ちいいの?
Okay, okay.
いいよ、いいよ
Ha, don't stop!
はぁ、止めんなよ!
Hey!
おい!
What’s that sound?
何の音だよ!
You have a cute face.
お前、可愛い顔だいなしだな
Do you have anything to say?
ちゃんと言うことあるの?
Thank you for the meal.
ごちそうさまでした
Hydrate quickly.
早く水分補給して
So, shall we play the game again?
じゃあ、またゲームするか?
Sit in the middle, in the middle, in the middle.
真ん中、真ん中、真ん中に座れよ
Look, look.
ほ ら、ほら
You were good again, so here we go.
またお前が良かったから、ほら
Well then, there you go.
じゃあ、ほら
Also, we had a little drink together.
また、ちょっと一緒におられた飲み合いこそ
I want to drink either one.
どっちでも飲みたい
Choose!
選べよ!
Do people who lose at rock, paper, scissors drink?
じゃんけんで負けたやつが飲むか
This is fine.
これでいいぞ
Don't bother.
め んどくせえよ
From the beginning, it's you today.
最初から、 今日は お前だな
I'll drink it.
飲 むよ
I'll make sure to drink it properly.
ちゃんと飲んでやるから
It seems like it's a hindrance.
邪魔だらしいよ
what happened?
どうしたの?
Okay.
よし
Well, next time, I'll reform the MG on the phone, and give it some support.Which one?
じゃあ次、電話で MG改革して あしろげをあしろげて どっち
The test is to see if you can endure it.
を 我慢できるか勝負
Shall we go?
行こうか
You like this, don't you?
これ好きだろ、お前
Anything is possible.
なんでもしいだろ
It's like, ``I should feel better.''
もっと気持ちよくなれよ、みたいな
If you speak up, I'll give you more money.
声出したらもっと金増やしてやるよ
It's a permission system.
許可制だろ
I'll allow it.
許可するんやろ
It's so easy to get to.
行きやすいんだな、そんなに
Do you always go around like this?
いつもこんなにおなりで行ってんのかよ、
you.
お前
How many times have you been there?
何回行ったんだ?
何回行ったかいれよ
Why don't you remember?
なんで覚えてないんだ?
I don't know.
わかんないです
Shall we go again then?
じゃあもう1回行くか
Osenma Center is Imarocho.
おせんまセンター、いまろちょんだよ、
We are.
俺らは
Isn't that a big deal?
きっぷりじゃねえかよ
Yes, yes, you have good sense.
うん うん、センスあるよ
good.
いいぞ
Is it your account?
お帳か
Is it the book?
お帳やっか
Do you know what it is?
何だかわかるか?